http://www.accucut.com/pages/privacy-policy

My Account
Cart (0)
Your cart is empty.
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Statement discloses the privacy practices for the entire Web Site. If you have questions regarding this statement, contact AccuCut Customer Service at (800) 288-1670 or (402) 934-1070.
AccuCut's Privacy Policy
Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. Because we gather certain types of information about AccuCut users, we want you to understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it.
Information that AccuCut Gathers
AccuCut gathers two types of information about users:
Personal data, provided through voluntary registration
Aggregated data, which tracks users as a whole
Personal data may be requested when you create an online account on accucut.com or register for contests, sweepstakes or other promotional programs. We ask for this in order to provide you with the best Web experience possible. This information might include member name, password, address and/or country information. Except as described below, it is not disclosed to parties other than AccuCut and its parent companies in any way that personally identifies you without your prior permission.
Aggregated data, which tracks AccuCut user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis, is gathered through several methods. This tracking data follows AccuCut traffic in general, and is not used to identify you personally. Aggregated tracking information helps us to determine which areas of our site users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. AccuCut does not track what you read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We may disclose such aggregated information to third parties such as our advertisers and partners.
How AccuCut Uses Information
AccuCut uses any personal information that's voluntarily given by you in order to enhance your experience, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the site or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.
AccuCut will not disclose any information that personally identifies you to parties other than AccuCut and its parent companies without your consent. There are exceptions:
When the purpose and manner of disclosure is clearly defined in advance.
When we believe in good faith that disclosure is legally required or to protect our rights.
Contests and Sweepstakes
AccuCut occasionally offers contests and sweepstakes in which we request certain personal information on a voluntary basis. These contests and sweepstakes are conducted in full accordance with United States federal and state laws. The full rules and all information about such contests are clearly posted during the event, including how information gathered will be used.
Search Terms
As a measure of user interest, we track search terms that are entered into our site. We create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns to improve shopping and user experiences.
Cookies and Tracking
A cookie is a small data file that Web sites commonly write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file contains information that can identify you anonymously in order to track traffic patterns on our site. The data is encrypted for your added security. AccuCut uses cookies as a way to measure activity on the site in order to continually improve your experience.
Cookies don't identify you personally, but rather identify your computer when you visit our site. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.
Your browser can be set to warn you before accepting cookies. In this case, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You can choose to refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use AccuCut, but you will need them for customizable areas of the site. AccuCut does allow users to clear cookies.
Electronic Newsletters
AccuCut offers free, electronic newsletters as a service to our users, based on a voluntary subscription. You will only receive a newsletter if you have requested it during registration to several areas of AccuCut or directly from our sign-up form. We do not share newsletter mailing lists with any third parties.
Changes to Policy
AccuCut reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying guests of the existence of a revised privacy policy.
Opt-Out Policy
You may terminate your subscription to our electronic newsletter at any time via e-mail by following the instructions contained at the end of every newsletter.
If you have questions about your information, please contact AccuCut Customer Service (800) 288-1670 or (402) 934-1070.
